#### Contact

tolani.oyefule@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/toyefule (LinkedIn)

# Top Skills

Epic Systems

Healthcare Information Technology
Java

# Languages

Yoruba (Limited Working)

English (Native or Bilingual)

Spanish (Full Professional)

### Certifications

Webpack for React Applications
Learning Node.js
Learning Scala Web Development
React: ES6, ES2016, and Beyond

## Honors-Awards

Cyber Security Certificate
Data Analytics Certificate

# Tolani Oyefule

Software Consultant, Healthcare Informaticist & Creative Engineer Philadelphia

# Summary

Healthcare Data Scientist with experience working in independently and within team settings. Characteristically, strong work ethic, able to multi task and balance a rigorous work schedule. Skilled in interpersonal interactions with diverse individuals through community service and remote communication.

Available for projects in 2020. EMR consultant with experience in Epic; Ambulatory, Ambulatory Curriculum Design, Ambulatory MST Build, ASAP, Beacon (Oncology) and Kaleidoscope, Healthy Planet, Coordinated Care Management (CoCM), classroom training and team lead experience.

# Experience

Safe Meadow

Network Administrator

February 2015 - July 2020 (5 years 6 months)

Greater Philadelphia Area

**Amazon Logistics** 

Associate

October 2019 - February 2020 (5 months)

King of Prussia

### Divurgent

5 years 8 months

Information Technology Team Lead

February 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 11 months)

Greater Boston Area

Lead a 45 consultant team integrating Cadence, Beacon, and Ambulatory Epic modules

**Epic Healthcare Consultant** 

#### May 2014 - March 2018 (3 years 11 months)

Greater Philadelphia Area

### **Epic**

Consulting Specialist May 2014 - October 2019 (5 years 6 months)

#### CSI Healthcare IT

Opthalmology Implementation Specialist November 2017 - December 2017 (2 months)

Ophthalmology Lead Implementation Specialist

The HCI Group Epic Analyst April 2017 - June 2017 (3 months)

Riverside Health System
Senior Implementation Specialist
September 2016 - March 2017 (7 months)

Richmond, Virginia Area

Identified cross-over issues between database services
Facilitated the Archival and retrieval of Patient care information
Collaborated with client leadership on development of Specific Features

Roper St. Francis Cerner Implementation Consultant October 2016 - November 2016 (2 months)

North Charleston, South Carolina

- •Provided elbow support to Physicians, Nurses and Clerical staff.
- •Trained Providers on Use of Powerchart and Dragon Dictation Software
- •Supported PowerChart, DynamicDoc, SurgiNet and Capacity Management.

Cerner Corporation
Consultant
June 2014 - September 2016 (2 years 4 months)

St. Luke's University Health Network IT Implementation Specialist 2015 - 2016 (1 year)

Debugged virtual environment following Implementation of site-wide enterprise Architecture

Developed patient-specific features to rectify prescription Information Managed Project Scheduling

Lowe's Companies, Inc.
Hardware Sales associate
October 2008 - May 2015 (6 years 8 months)
Plymouth Meeting, Pennsylvania

Assistant to the Management Staff in building materials & inside Lawn and Garden.

Paint brand embassador

Product test Engineer and in-house assembly team for outside Lawn and Garden

Tools and Hardware solutions specialist specific to Independent Contractors of building materials.

# Education

Penn State University

B.Sc., Telecommunications · (2012 - 2016)

Montgomery College

Certificate of Completion, Advanced Data Analytics · (2019 - 2019)

Montgomery College

Java Bootcamp, Computer Science · (2018 - 2019)

Montgomery College

Certificate of Completion, Data Analytics · (2019 - 2019)

Montgomery College

Certificate of Completion, Cyber/Computer Forensics and

Counterterrorism · (2019 - 2019)